我不知道该怎么看待这起案子
I don't know what to make of this case,
感觉我花了半辈子的时间 听他们俩在法庭上的陈述
and I seem to have spent half my life listening to these two in courtrooms.
很难理解一个本该爱你的人
It's hard to understand why someone that is supposed to love you
怎么会那么残忍
could be that cruel.
他一脚踢在我背上
He just kicked me in the back.
我不知道该相信谁
I don't know who to believe.
没那回事
It... It didn't happen.
我不知道有多少是真的 他们两个都是演员
I don't know how much of it is true. They're two actors.
你真的能感觉到这个女人有多变态
You can really just feel how much of a psychopath this woman is!
陪审团正在讨论
Jury deliberations are underway
约翰尼・德普和安柏・赫德的诽谤案
in the Johnny Depp and Amber Heard defamation trial.
-我为判决感到紧张 -那是抖音的审判
- I've never been this nervous for a verdict. - ...a TikTok trial.
我们为什么这么着迷？
Why are we all so fascinated?
因为他们是名人 还是因为细节？
Because they're famous, because of the details?
以上皆是
I think it's all of the above.
陪审团的审判应该关注法律和事实
Jury trials are supposed to focus on law and facts.
陪审团只会听取正式提交的证据
The jury hears what's submitted into evidence.
我没再见他了
I don't see him anymore.
你真是幼稚！成熟点吧！
You are such a baby! Grow the fuck up!
你们抓错人了
You've got the wrong girl.
陪审团没看到什么？
What didn't the jury see?
佩妮法官解封了45份文件
Forty-five documents were unsealed by Judge Penney.
-早上好 -这太疯狂了
- Good morning. - This is so wild.
一个女生可以习惯这个
A girl could get used to this.
审判期间有不允许什么吗？
What wasn't allowed during the course of this trial?
我们应该还会再见
Have a feeling we will see each other again.
《德普 vs 赫德： 好莱坞夫妻诽谤案》
剧名：《第三集：判决爆红》
谢谢 女士们 先生们 你们可以坐下了
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. You may be seated.
你的下一位证人
All right, your next witness.
被告传唤安柏・赫德
Your Honor, defendant calls Amber Heard.
-提醒一下 你是宣过誓的 -当然
A reminder, Ms. Heard, you're still under oath.
-谢谢 -谢谢
- Of course, Your Honor. Thank you. - Thank you.
你的问题？
All right, your question?
你在公众面前遭受了怎样的折磨？
How have you suffered publicly?
反对 纯属臆测
Objection, speculation.
反对无效
Overruled.
我被骚扰
I am harassed...
安柏是个骗子
Amber's a liar. Amber's...
安柏来了
That's Amber.
被羞辱
...humiliated...
我只是坐在地毯上
I was just sitting there on this... on... on this carpet,
看着脏地毯
looking at the dirty carpet,
思考我是怎么倒在这块地毯上的
wondering how I wound up on this carpet.
每天都在遭受威胁
...threatened every single day.
人们想杀我
People want to kill me.
有人想把我的宝宝放进微波炉
People want to put my baby in the microwave,
他们会这样跟我说
and they tell me that.
你在这场庭审中 听到赫德小姐的证词 有什么感受？
What has it been like for you to listen to Ms. Heard's testimony at this trial?
听到…
It's...
听到她把那些
It's insane to hear
令人发指的暴力指控
heinous accusations of violence,
性暴力
sexual violence,
归结于我 拿来指控我
that she's attributed to me, that she's accused me of.
这太可怕了
This is horrible.
太痛苦了
This is painful.
任何人经历这种事 都会觉得被羞辱
And this is humiliating for any human being to go through.
也许大家很容易忘记这一点
And perhaps it's easy to forget that,
但我也是一个人
but I'm a human being.
冷酷
Brutal.
残忍
Cruel.
而且完全不属实
and all... false.
完全不属实
All false.
我只想让约翰尼放过我
I just want Johnny to leave me alone.
我只想让他放过我
I just want him to leave me alone.
我觉得这看起来令人不适
I just find the whole thing uncomfortable to watch.
-我心思完全没放在这上面 -那你什么都不能说
- I haven't plugged into it at all. - Oh, then you can't say anything.
-我不想看到这么私人的… -这就像私人丑事 不是吗？
- I don't really wanna see such intimate detail of...- It is a bit of sort of dirty... dirty laundry, isn't it?
-对 -就像电影
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's like a movie.
-是的 -而且这些指控都很严重
Yeah, and these are really serious allegations here.
但它在我们眼前变得戏剧化了
But it has become kind of dramatized, you know, before our very eyes.
陪审团很不容易 要决定谁是施暴者
The jury has a very, very tough job here trying to decide who the abuser is,
谁是受害者
who the victim is.
真是一场疯狂的审判
I mean, it... it's... it's really a wild trial here.
这不只是一起诽谤案 他们的任务非常艰巨
It's not just about defamation anymore. They really have a big, difficult job here.
只有一个人看到 约翰尼对安柏有肢体暴力行为
There's only one person to have ever witnessed Johnny be physically violent with Amber...
（丹尼尔戴利欧利 内容创作者 来自微醺前无罪播客）
…她的妹妹惠特尼赫德
And it's her little sister. Whitney Heard.
（突袭 内容创作者 来自YouTube突袭频道）
今天我们要调查楼梯事件的细节
Today we'll be digging into all the nitty-gritty of the staircase incident
涉及约翰尼 安柏和她的妹妹惠特尼
with Johnny, Amber, and her sister, Whitney.
这件事发生在 澳大利亚事件后一周左右
This happened about a week after the Australia incident.
这应该是所谓的“楼梯事件”
Uh, I believe that this is from w-w-w-what's been called the "staircase incident."
（2016年5月 赫德申请离婚 2022年4月 美国审判）
我醒来 看到安柏在我的卧室 说：“他出轨了 你敢相信吗？”
I woke up to Amber in my bedroom saying, "Can you believe he's cheating on me?"
我下去跟他聊天 他显然喝醉了
I went down there to talk to him, and I can tell he's clearly drunk.
我发现他的平板电脑开着
I found his iPad open.
他在跟人发短信
He was texting someone.
他在给一个 跟他有性关系的女人发短信
He was texting this woman, um, that he had had a sexual relationship with.
我看到他在我们结婚后去她家
I saw that he had gone to her house after we got married.
难以置信的痛苦
Unbelievably painful.
你还记得赫德女士 那时候因为什么而生气吗？
Do you recall what Ms. Heard was upset about at this time?
我不记得 真的不记得
I do not. I really don't.
安柏和我在夹层楼上
Amber and I are on the little mezzanine.
厨房在下面 夹层在上面
The kitchen's down here, and the mezzanine's up here.
他说她是贱人婊子 用过的垃圾袋之类的
You know, he's calling her a "fucking whore," "fucking cunt," "used-up trash bag." You know, whatever.
他们互相说很可怕的话 她说他又老又肥
They were saying horrible things to one another. She was calling him "old and fat."
他冲上了楼梯
He bolted up the stairs.
惠特尼 她的妹妹也在
Whitney, her sister, was there, who...
她出面阻止
...who stepped in the way.
他从我背后接近
He comes up behind me,
攻击了我后背的这个位置
strikes me in the back kind of just somewhere over here.
我听到安柏大喊：“别打我妹妹”
I hear Amber shout, "Don't hit my fucking sister."
安柏溜过来
Amber snuck in the...
她伸手全力挥过来 打在我颧骨上
She... reached and got the roundhouse in and nailed me on the cheek bone.
（安柏・赫德声称她打约翰尼・德普 是为了保护她的妹妹）
那个时候
By that time,
约翰尼已经用一只手抓住了安柏的头发
Johnny had already grabbed Amber by the hair with one hand
并且用另一只手反复打她的脸
and was whacking her repeatedly in the face with the other,
我就站在那里
as I was standing there.
这是唯一一个目击证人 安柏的妹妹
It is the only instance where a witness, Amber's sister,
声称她亲眼目睹约翰尼・德普
is claiming to have actually witnessed firsthand assault
进行了被指控的攻击
alleged against Johnny Depp.
…用一只手抓住安柏的头发
...grabbed Amber by the hair with one hand
并且用另一只手反复打她的脸
and was whacking her repeatedly in the face with the other.
我没有犹豫 没有等待 我就是脑子里
I don't hesitate, I don't wait, I just, in my head,
立刻想到凯特・莫斯和楼梯
instantly think of Kate Moss and the stairs.
（利莫尔律师 爱与秩序播客主播）
赫德在她本人的证词中 提到凯特・莫斯
Amber Heard, in her direct testimony, mentioned Kate Moss.
发生了一件让互联网疯狂的有趣的事
One interesting thing that's happened that, now, the Internet's going crazy over
是他转身跟他的律师同伴碰了下拳
is he turned and gave a... like, did a fist-pump...right to his co-counsel.
（迈克尔・莫斯 联邦检察官 爱与秩序播客嘉宾）
审判法里有个概念叫“开门”
There's a concept in trial law called "opening the door."
比如“也许我们都同意 有些东西是不相关的”
Like, "Maybe there's something we both agree is irrelevant."
（凯特・莫斯在家等着上证人席）
“这对我的案子有好处
But, on my side of things, it would help me and help my case,
但因为法官裁定存在偏见 所以我不能提”
but I know I can't bring it up, because the judge says it's irrelevant, or it's too prejudicial, or whatever.
别这么说
Don't say that.
凯特・莫斯和楼梯
Kate Moss and the stairs.
是约翰尼・德普先注意到的
Johnny Depp picked up on it first, actually.
他笑得好像“真不敢相信她这么说”
He smiled like, "I can't believe she just said that,"
因为这打开了门 凯特・莫斯不打算作证
because it opened the door. Kate Moss was not going to testify.
这是个关键时刻 因为它使得
This was a real pivotal moment because this allowed
本杰明・楚和卡米尔・巴斯克斯 都可以说没有其他人受到了伤害
both Ben Chew and Camille Vasquez to say that there are no other victims here, right?
你以为他会把你妹妹扔下楼梯
You thought he was gonna throw your sister down the stairs
就像他把凯特・莫斯 扔下楼梯一样 是吗？
like he had thrown Kate Moss down the stairs, right?
他对着惠特尼挥拳了 而且我听过传闻
He swung at Whitney, and I'd heard a rumor,
关于这件事的一个模糊的传闻
a vague rumor, about that.
所以我会这么想
And so it's what I thought of.
如果凯特・莫斯过来说
If Kate Moss were to come in and say,
“约翰尼从来没有 对我有过肢体或任何暴力”
"No, Johnny was never physically abusive or anything to me,"
那么这对安柏的说辞 会有毁灭性的打击
then that would be a really big, detrimental thing to Amber's case.
陪审员们被告知 “评估可信度是你们的职责”
Jurors are told, "It's your job to evaluate credibility."
如果你发现一个人在一件事上撒了谎
And, you know, if you find someone is lying on one issue,
你就可以判断他们是骗子
you can conclude they're liars in general.
我知道约翰尼的真相
I know the truth about Johnny.
（凯特・莫斯 超模）
（荒岛唱片节目音频 BBC广播4台）
德普和莫斯之间的关系
The relationship between Johnny Depp and Kate Moss.
媒体界的很多人 在他们还在约会的时候
A lot of people in the media, back then when they were dating,
将之视为一种不稳定的关系
it was looked at as somewhat of a volatile relationship.
德普因为破坏酒店房间而被捕
Johnny Depp was arrested for trashing a hotel room.
（演员破坏酒店后获释）
我相信公平和正义
I believe in fairness and justice.
我相信真相
I believe in the truth.
约翰尼！
Johnny!
早安 女士们 先生们 请坐 下一位证人
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen. Please be seated. Your next witness.
早上好 法官大人
Good morning, Your Honor.
德普先生请凯特・莫斯上证人席
Um, Mr. Depp calls Kate Moss to the stand.
谢谢 举起你的右手
Thank you, ma'am. If you could raise your right hand.
你是否发誓或确认 在法律的惩罚下说实话？
Do you swear or affirm to tell the truth under penalty of law?
-是的 -谢谢
- I do. - Thank you.
请问莫斯小姐 你和德普先生的 感情关系持续了多久？
For how long, Ms. Moss, were you and Mr. Depp a romantic couple?
1994年到1998年
Ninety-four to 1998.
你和德普先生 如果有的话 在牙买加时发生了什么？
What, if anything, happened when you were in Jamaica with Mr. Depp?
我们准备离开房间
We were leaving the room,
在我离开房间时 我滑下了楼梯
and, as I left the room, I slid down the stairs
弄伤了我的背
and I hurt my back.
德普先生有没有把你推下楼？
Did Mr. Depp push you in any way down the stairs?
没有
No.
在你们交往的过程中 他有没有把你推下楼过？
During the course of your relationship, did he ever push you down any stairs?
没有 他从没推过我
No, he never pushed me,
踢我 或者把我扔下过任何楼梯
kicked me, or threw me... ...down any stairs.
谢谢你 莫斯小姐
Thank you, Ms. Moss.
非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you.
这些陪审员应该听
These jurors are supposed to be listening
法庭上的每一个词
to every single word of everything that's going on.
问题在于 他们可能会停止听你的话
The problem is they might stop listening to you
因为在那个时候
because, at that moment,
他们不再觉得你是可信的了
they no longer find you credible.
那一刻对安柏・赫德极其不利
That moment was very damaging for Amber Heard.
我不知道陪审团在想什么 但如果这是一场可信度的游戏
Don't know what the jury is thinking, but if it's a credibility game,
这也的确是
which it is,
那他们可能已经 不会再听她的任何陈述了…
they may have tuned out to the rest of her case...
…用另一只手猛击她的脸
...whacking her repeatedly in the face with the other.
…就因为那一刻
...because of that very moment.
这起案子的依据是
This... This case rests on the sentence.
那篇文章的第一句话
The first sentence of that... of that article.
-是的 -“我变成了家庭暴力的代言人”
- Yeah. - "I was...I was... I became the face of domestic violence."
这起案子其实是
And the case really is, the lawyers' case is,
“我们要证明你说的一切都是假的”
"We are gonna prove that everything you said is not true."
（布莱恩・卡伦 喜剧演员和演员 PBD播客嘉宾）
（为挑战赫德 关于虐待的指控 德普的律师）
好了 你的下一位证人
All right, your next witness.
“这是你编的”
"You're making this stuff up."
说出你的全名以供记录
Could you state your full name for the record?
-香农・库里 -你的职业是什么？
- Shannon Curry. - What do you do for a living?
我是一名临床和法证心理学家
I am a clinical and forensic psychologist.
你是怎么参与到这起案子的？
How'd you get involved in this case?
德普先生的律师请我
I was asked, uh, by counsel for Mr. Depp
来对赫德小姐进行心理评估
to provide a psychological evaluation of Ms. Heard.
你有没有被要求 对德普先生做心理评估？
Were you ever asked to do a psychological evaluation of Mr. Depp?
没有
No.
在审理期间 双方都将心理健康和药物成瘾
During the trial, both sides have been using mental health and substance addiction
作为对付另一方的武器
as weapons against the other team.
通常情况下 提起诉讼的一方
And what usually happens is the people bringing the case
都会有一名心理健康专家
usually have a mental health expert
诊断对方患有严重精神健康障碍
diagnosing the opposing person with a bad mental health disorder.
赫德小姐的评估支持两种诊断
The results of Ms. Heard's evaluation supported two diagnoses,
即边缘型人格障碍和组织型人格障碍
borderline personality disorder and histrionic personality disorder.
然后为自己的辩护的人
And then the person defending themselves in the trial will typically try to say,
通常会说：“我没有那么糟糕的诊断
"No, no, no, I don't have that bad diagnosis."
我有能让陪审团和观众 更加同情的病症
"I have something that evokes more pity from a jury and an audience,
比如创伤后应激障碍”
something like PTSD."
我和赫德小姐总共会见了约29小时
Okay, so I met with Ms. Heard, um, for a total of about 29 hours.
主要意见是赫德小姐 对亲密伴侣的暴力行为的报告
The main opinion is that Ms. Heard's report of intimate partner violence
跟我们实践中遇到的 亲密伴侣暴力行为是一致的
is consistent with what we know in the field about intimate partner violence,
赫德小姐表现出
and that Ms. Heard demonstrated
非常明显的心理和创伤影响
very clear psychological and traumatic effects.
那么你是否得出了任何诊断结论？
And did you arrive at any diagnostic conclusions?
我诊断赫德小姐患有创伤后应激障碍
I diagnosed, uh, Ms. Heard with post-traumatic stress disorder.
赫德小姐没有创伤后应激障碍
Ms. Heard did not have PTSD,
也有相当明显的迹象表明
and there were also pretty significant indications
她严重夸大了创伤后应激障碍的症状
that she was grossly exaggerating symptoms of PTSD.
我们知道 如果有人在童年时期遭到虐待
We know that if somebody suffers childhood abuse as a child,
他们就会更容易患上创伤后应激障碍
they're much more likely, then, to be more vulnerable to getting PTSD.
她在一个暴力家庭长大
She was raised in a family of violence.
她被她父亲肢体虐待
She was physically abused by her father,
她看到她的父亲虐待她的母亲
uh, she saw her father abuse her mother,
她的父母都饱受药物滥用的折磨
and both her parents also struggled with substance abuse very significantly,
所以她从小就学会如何照顾人
so she had learned from a very early age how to caretake.
说到演员 戏剧性会是一大关键特质
When it comes to histrionic, a lot of the key features are going to be drama,
对不成为关注焦点感到极度不舒服
extreme discomfort with not being the center of attention,
极力想成为关注焦点
extreme efforts to be the center of attention,
当他们觉得自己不是关注的焦点时
and when they feel that they're not the center of attention,
你会看到他们编造故事试图获得关注
you will see making up stories to try to get attention,
经常扮演受害者或公主的角色
often taking on a victim or a princess role.
她学会了去爱伤害她的人
She learned that she could love someone who hurts her.
她知道了伤害她的人可以是爱她的
She knew that people who hurt her also can love her.
它还代表了能在情感之间快速转变
It also represented the quick shifts you'll see between emotions.
所以 她可能一下是这样
So, she would suddenly be one way,
然后突然改变主意
and then she would become very animated.
进行观察的人会觉得这几乎是在演戏
People who are observing them will feel like, uh, it's almost playacting.
这变成了大家是否认为她说谎
It became about whether people thought she was lying,
她在证人席上的表现 她是不是显得心里有鬼
how Heard was acting on the stand, the way she looked shifty.
（阿雅・罗曼诺 文化记者 说出三首歌播客音频）
当事件像滚雪球一样变大
As it sort of snowballed out of control,
这就不再是简单的是非题了
it became much, much, much, much less about that actual simple yes-no question,
她能说自己是家庭暴力的受害者吗？
"Can she call herself a victim of domestic abuse?"
让我们回到飞机事件 据称那次德普踢了赫德
Let's go back to the... there was a plane incident where Depp allegedly kicked Amber Heard on a plane.
我记得是在2014年
I believe it was in 2014.
回到那个事件
Just going back to the incident
德普和赫德在一架飞机上吵架
where Depp and Heard got in a fight on an airplane.
我要跟你们聊聊波士顿飞机事件
So I'm going to take you to the Boston plane incident.
我们原计划回洛杉矶给他女儿过生日
The plan, we'd go back to L.A. for his daughter's birthday.
我上了飞机
And I get on the plane.
我身体的每一个细胞 都知道有点不对劲
And I, uh, ju... I just knew in every cell of my body something was wrong.
回到那一件事
Just boil it down to that one incident.
所有的细节
All the little details, like,
跟证明犯罪是否发生无关
don't really have anything to do with proving whether a crime happened.
目标是证明她在说谎
The goal is to prove that she's lying.
-早安 怀亚特先生 -早上好
- Good morning, Mr. Wyatt. - Good morning.
怀亚特先生 德普先生在那班飞机上喝酒了吗？
Mr. Wyatt, was Mr. Depp consuming any alcohol on that flight?
当然 喝了
Sure. Yes.
他看起来醉了吗？
Did he seem intoxicated?
看起来醉了？
"Seem intoxicated"? I...
不 他就是约翰尼的样子
No, he seemed like Johnny.
不 他看起来很正常
No, he seemed normal.
他散发着大麻和酒精的味道
He reeks of weed and alcohol.
我是说 他的口气好难闻
I mean, his breath smelled so bad.
她摆脸色给约翰尼看
Well, she was giving Johnny the cold shoulder,
非常安静 看起来气鼓鼓的
being quiet, and, uh, you know, seemed pouty.
我们前一天晚上吵架了
We had argued the night before.
她就是在找架吵
She was looking for a fight,
我吃了两片阿片药物
and I had taken two
洛西考酮
of these, um, opiates, these Roxicodones.
他因为我接了 跟詹姆斯弗兰科对戏的工作而生气
He was mad at me for taking the job with James Franco.
安柏！
Amber!
他恨詹姆斯・弗兰科
He hated James Franco.
所以他问我激情戏拍得怎样
So he, um, is asking me about how the sex scene went,
问詹姆斯・弗兰科 在那场戏里做了什么
to asking me what James Franco had done in the scene.
他说了关于我身体的很恶心的话
He was saying really disgusting things about my body,
说我很享受
about how I liked it.
他在很多人面前说我是荡妇
He called me a slut in front of people.
你看德普先生和赫德小姐 看得有多清楚？
To what extent were you able to see Mr. Depp and Ms. Heard?
我看得很清楚
Uh, i-it... it... I was able to see them very clearly.
德普先生有没有 对赫德女士说很可怕的话？
Wasn't Mr. Depp saying pretty horrible things to Ms. Heard?
我没有这个印象
I don't recall that.
比如“在片场挨操”？
Like, "Get fucked on set"?
“被他妈的詹姆斯弗兰科操”？
"Get fucked with fucking James fucking Franco"?
-你有没有听到这些话？ -我没有印象
- Did you hear that? - I don't recall.
你有没有听到他说 “至少你很他妈享受”？
Did you hear him say, "At least you fucking liked it"?
没有
No.
你有没有听到他说： “我猜你偷伸舌头还喜欢吧？”
Did you hear him say, "I bet you slipped a tongue in there and liked it"?
没有
No.
你有没有听到他
Did you hear him say...
提到安柏的阴部 问她是不是阴部湿了？
make references to Amber's pussy, and asking if her pussy was wet?
法官大人 根据不足 骚扰
Your Honor, lack of foundation, harassment.
你有没有听过上述任何一句？
Did you hear any of that?
-我没这个印象 -好了 裁决反对意见吧
- No, not that I recall. - Overrule the objection.
我在某个时候起身
I, at some point in this, get up.
离开了他
I walk away from him.
我背对着他 我感觉到一只靴子
My back is turned to him, and I feel this... boot
踩在我的背上
in my back.
他踢了我的背
He just kicked me in the back.
我心想
And I... I didn't...I thought to myself,
“操 我不知道该怎么做”
"Fuck. I don't know what to do."
没人说话或做任何事
No one said anything, no one did anything.
飞机上落针可闻
It was like you could h...You could hear a pin drop on that plane.
你能感觉到紧张气氛 但没人采取任何行动
You could feel the tension, but no one did anything.
我觉得非常难堪 他就那样当着所有人的面
I felt so embarrassed that he could kick me to the ground
把我踢到地上
in front of people.
如果有的话 你在多大程度上
To what extent, if any,
看到德普先生或赫德小姐 在飞机上互相殴打
did you observe Mr. Depp or Ms. Heard hit, kick,
脚踢或者互扔东西？
or throw anything at each other on the plane?
不 我完全没看到过
No, I don't recall that at all.
他越来越糟糕
As he got worse,
甚至向空乘员索要氧气瓶
he demanded the oxygen tank from the flight attendants.
你和德普先生 在波士顿的飞机上共用了一个氧气瓶
You shared an oxygen tank with Mr. Depp on that Boston plane.
-不是吗？ -不是
- Didn't you? - No.
他继续喝酒
He continued to drink,
然后开始像动物一样嚎叫
and then eventually, um, started howling like an animal.
然后在洗手间里晕倒了
And passed out in the bathroom...
门锁着
...with the door locked.
（法庭证据 安柏・赫德的录音 2014年5月）
怀亚特先生 你有没有看到德普先生
Mr. Wyatt, did you see Mr. Depp,
去飞机后面晕倒并且大声呻吟？
uh, go to the back of the plane and pass out and moan loudly?
-我没有印象 -这个也没有印象？
- I don't recall that. - You don't recall that either?
-没有 -好
- No. - Okay.
你和德普先生一起下的飞机吗？
Did you leave the plane with Mr. Depp?
我去了自己的家
I went to my own home.
好 德普先生当时状态如何？
Okay, and what was Mr. Depp's state?
我不记得了
I don't recall.
你不记得他当时是否昏倒了？
You don't recall if he was passed out or not?
不
No.
你今天坐在这里 宣过誓
As you're sitting here today, under oath,
你真的不记得德普先生有没有晕倒？
you honestly can't remember if Mr. Depp was passed out?
我不知道
I don't know.
德普先生是有可能 在飞机上踢安柏的 对吧？
And Mr. Depp could have kicked Amber on that plane, right?
我没看到
Not that I saw.
你下飞机时
When you got off the plane from Boston, you knew Ms. Heard
知道赫德小姐在生你的气 对吧？
was angry with you, didn't you?
她总是很生气 是的
She was always angry, yes.
你问了杜特斯先生
And you asked Mr. Deuters... He was your personal assist...
他是你的私人助理 对吧？
Mr. Deuters was your personal assistant, correct?
杜特斯先生是其中之一 是的 先生
Yeah, Mr. Deuters was one of them, yes, sir.
你不是第一次请杜特斯先生
Right, and it wasn't uncommon for you to ask Mr. Deuters
代表你跟赫德小姐沟通 是吧？
to communicate with Ms. Heard on your behalf, correct?
我的所有私人助理都代表我
It wasn't uncommon for any of them to communicate,
跟赫德小姐沟通过
uh, with Ms. Heard on my behalf.
杜特斯没有作证
Deuters never testified.
德普第二次站上证人席
So with Depp on the witness stand for the second time,
在赫德的辩护律师试图
here's what happened when Amber Heard's defense attorney
将德普助理发的短信 给陪审团看时 发生了这样的事
tried to show texts from Depp's assistant to the jury.
能请拿出229号证物吗？
Can you pull up Exhibit 229, please?
根据德普先生的证词 我提请采纳229号证物
Based on Mr. Depp's testimony, I'd ask to move for the admission of Exhibit 229.
-法官大人 我们能上前吗？ -当然
Your Honor...can we please approach? - Sure.
（赫德的律师请求来自）
（阿兹卡瑞特法官的许可 以提交额外证据）
（社交媒体评论员 密切关注这一决定）
聊天室有人说 如果我们看到杜特斯的短信
Some people are saying in the chat that Deuters' texts, if that's what we're about to see,
这会对德普不利
they're... they're not gonna look good for Johnny.
英国的审判里也出现了
Came up in the UK trial as well. Um...
有关踢安柏的事情
About ki... Uh, something about kicking Amber.
（陪审团没有看到短信）
（阿兹卡瑞特法官没有允许采纳）
-他们没能让杜特斯的短信被采纳 -好
- They didn't get that Deuters stuff in. - Okay.
在跟法官磋商后
After that sidebar,
本・罗腾伯恩律师放弃了
attorney Ben Rottenborn moves on,
那些短信没有成为证据
and those texts stay out of evidence.
这起案子里有太多证据
You know, there was so much evidence in this case.
在预审听证会上 他们必须裁定哪些是可接受的
In the pre-trial hearings, they have to, you know, rule what is admissible,
哪些不是 所以当进入庭审时 可以加快进度
what isn't, just so that when we get to trial, we can, you know, speed things along,
只留下庭审的关键证据 以供陪审员下定决心
only have what's, you know, essential for the trial, for the jurors to make up their mind.
你为什么会想要排除证据？
Why would you want to exclude evidence?
因为它会伤害你 这就是原因
Because it hurts you. That's why.
德普是一位大师级演员 兄弟
Depp is a master actor, dude.
他几乎不用动就能引诱我们所有人
He seduced all of us by barely moving.
要不要把艺术和人品分开 取决于你
It's your decision whether you want to separate the art from the artist.
（马特沃顿 演员 PBD播客嘉宾）
约翰尼・德普是很棒的演员 但我也觉得他是热爱暴力的人
I think Johnny Depp is a terrific actor. I also happen to think he's a violent lover.
除了这些可怕的指控之外 他还是很讨人喜欢的 对吧？
He's a likeable guy, other than these horrific allegations, right?
大家都喜欢 他在《加勒比海盗》里的角色
Everybody loved him in The Pirates of the Caribbean,
他总是带着一些光环
and there's a little bit of what's called a halo effect around him.
（安柏赫德的律师团队 转变了提问思路）
（转而质疑约翰尼德普的人品）
所以这些照片、短信和证词 是具有毁灭性的
But that's why these photos, the texts, the testimony, is so devastating,
因为这会打破我们对德普先生的看法
because it shatters that perception we have of Mr. Depp.
保罗贝坦尼 是跟你一起嗑药的好朋友 对吧？
Paul Bettany's a good friend that you've done drugs with, right?
这是个奇怪的问题
That's a strange question.
保罗贝塔尼是我的好朋友 是的
Um, Paul Bettany's a good friend. Yes.
你们当时都非常喜欢 使用管制药物和酒精
The two of you shared an enjoyment of controlled drugs and alcohol
是或不是？
at that time, yes or no?
是
Yes.
-你和他一起吸过毒？ -是的
- You've done drugs with him? - Yes, I have.
可卡因 对吧？
Cocaine, right?
可卡因 是的
Uh, cocaine, yes.
酒精
Alcohol.
酒精 是的
Alcohol, yes.
现在你在试着 表现得像个绅士了 是吗？
Now you try to conduct yourself as a gentleman, right?
是的
Yes, sir.
德普先生 这是你和保罗・贝坦尼
Mr. Depp, this is a text message exchange
在2013年6月11日的往来短信
that you had with Paul Bettany on June 11th, 2013.
你发短信给贝塔尼先生 “我们烧了安柏吧”
You text Mr. Bettany, "Let's burn Amber."
-你看到了吗？ -我看到了
- You see that? - I do see that.
下一条短信 你说
The next text down, you say...
“我们先把她淹死 然后烧了她
然后我会操她烧焦的尸体 以确保她死透了”
我没读错吧？
Did I read that right?
你完全没读错
You certainly did, yes.
你写的是之后成为了你妻子的女人
And you wrote that about the woman who would later become your wife.
没错
Yes, I did.
黑色幽默
Dark humor.
那些短信…
The text messages that... it...
抱歉每个人都要经历这些
I apologize that everyone's had to, uh, experience.
我为提到的一些内容感到羞耻
I am ashamed of, uh...of some of the references, uh, made.
我羞耻的是 当时
I'm, uh, embarrassed that, at the time,
在那个激动的时刻
the heat of the moment,
我当时感觉到的
the heat of the pain...
激烈的痛苦
um, that I was feeling,
让我变得黑暗
um, went to...went to dark places.
谢谢 大家请坐 结案陈词 罗腾伯恩先生？
Thank you, you may be seated. All right, closing arguments. Mr. Rottenborn?
-谢谢 -谢谢
- Thanks. - Okay, thank you.
大家早上好
Good morning everyone.
想想德普先生
Think about the message
和他的律师们试图对安柏
that Mr. Depp and his attorneys are sending to Amber,
以及每一位家暴受害者传达的信息
and by extension, to every victim of domestic abuse everywhere.
当德普先生提起这场诽谤诉讼
When Mr. Depp brought this case for defamation,
赫德女士全力以赴
Ms. Heard went all in.
她编出了一个令人震惊
She spun a story of shocking,
令人难以承受的残忍虐待故事
overwhelming, brutal abuse.
如果你没有拍照 就没发生过
"If you didn't take pictures, it didn't happen."
如果你拍了照 那就是假的
"If you did take pictures, they're fake."
她来到这间法庭 准备给出
She came into this courtroom prepared to
人生中最棒的表演 她也做到了
give the performance of her life, and she gave it.
你没有寻求医治 你没受伤
"You didn't seek medical treatment, you weren't injured."
如果你真的去找过医生
"If you did seek medical treatment,
那你就是疯了
you're crazy."
现在轮到你们了 陪审团
Now it's time for you, the jury,
你们来做决定
to come to a decision.
这场审判远不止 是约翰尼・德普和安柏・赫德的对峙
This trial is about so much more than Johnny Depp versus Amber Heard.
这场审判事关一个男人的好名声
What is at stake in this trial is a man's good name.
事关言论自由 为之挺身而出 保护它…
It's about the freedom of speech. Stand up for it, protect it...
当这场审判事关一个男人的生命
What is at stake at this trial is a man's life...
…否决德普先生针对安柏的指控
...and reject Mr. Depp's claims against Amber.
…他被指控 犯下可怕罪行时失去的人生…
...the life that he lost when he was accused of a heinous crime...
但他没有停在那里
But he doesn't stop there,
因为在德普先生的世界里 你不能离开德普先生
because in Mr. Depp's world, you don't leave Mr. Depp.
…以及他在证明 自己清白后可以过的人生
...and the life he could live when he is finally vindicated.
如果你这么做的话
And if you do,
他将在全球范围内 发起针对你的羞辱运动…
he will start a campaign of global humiliation against you...
德普先生虐待赫德小姐的 堆积如山的证据
The mountain of evidence that Mr. Depp abused Ms. Heard
根本不存在
is simply not there.
…一场绵延至今的抹黑运动
...a smear campaign that lasts to this very day.
要么他打了她无数次
Either he hit her countless times,
要么从她嘴里说出的话 你一句都不能信
or you can't believe a single word that comes out of her mouth.
他会尽全力毁掉你的生活
He will do everything he can to destroy your life,
毁掉你的事业
to destroy your career.
好了 现在已经不归我掌控了
All right. It is out of my hands.
只是提醒你们不要阅读 观看
So just a reminder that you're not to read anything about this case, you're not to watch anything about this case,
或听取关于这起案子的任何信息
you're not to listen to anything about this case.
这适用于电视、报纸、杂志
This applies to television, newspapers, magazines,
互联网和任何线上网站
the Internet, and any online sites.
你们不能在社交网站 博客或相似网站
Further, you're not to read, watch, or listen to anything about the case
阅读 观看或听取
on social media n... sites,
任何关于此案的信息
uh, any blogs, or similar sites.
你们不能和任何人交流这起案子
In addition, you must not communicate with anyone about the case...
今晚 随着他高调的诽谤案
Tonight, with his high-profile defamation case
交由陪审团裁决 约翰尼・德普放松下来了
now in the hands of the jury, Johnny Depp is letting his hair down.
这位演员在周五的爆炸性结案陈词后 在英国舞台上进行了表演
The actor, spotted performing on stage in England after explosive closing arguments Friday.
（约翰尼・德普在伦敦时 社交媒体上的争论升级了）
（大部分人似乎倾向于德普）
亲爱的约翰尼・德普 我支持你
Dear Johnny Depp, I stand with you.
-我支持你 -我支持你
I stand with you.
我支持你
抖音上 “为约翰尼・德普讨公道”的话题
On TikTok, the hashtag "Justice for Johnny Depp"
有将近200亿观看量
now has nearly 20 billion views,
而“为安柏・赫德讨公道”的话题
while the hashtag "Justice for Amber Heard"
有7750万观看量
has 77.5 million.
（我支持安柏・赫德）
好吧 我是
Well, I do.
（你是激进女权主义者？ 所以你支持安柏・赫德？）
（随着判决的临近 社交媒体上的紧张气氛越来越浓）
陪审团周末解散了 就是这样
Jury's been dismissed for the weekend, so that's it.
我们现在要度过一个漫长的周末 等待周二的到来 我们该做什么？
Now we have a long weekend and wait until Tuesday. What are we going to do?
我们可以得出几个结论 都不是很好
We can come to a few conclusions, none very good.
为了让你不那么焦虑 我会告诉你最新情况
To manage your anxiety, I'll keep you updated.
其他人害怕吗？
Guys, is anyone else freaking out?
我们必须等待一整个周末 才能看到案子的结果
We have to wait an entire weekend to see what's going on in this case.
抱歉镜头在晃动 但我现在很紧张
Sorry for shaking the camera but I am stressed.
我无法放松
I'm not gonna be able to relax now.
我整个周末都会想这件事 我太激动了
I'm gonna be thinking about this all weekend. I'm freaking out.
还需要多久？
How long is this going to take?
（判决日 弗吉尼亚）
如果你仔细想想
If you think about it, right now,
约翰尼・德普和公众 就像切尔诺贝利的土地一样有放射性
Johnny Depp and the public is about as radioactive as Chernobyl soil,
存在真正的风险 他不仅可能以原告的身份败诉
and there is a real risk that not only could he lose this case as the plaintiff,
而且赫德还对他 提起了一亿美元的反诉
but Heard has a $100 million counterclaim against him,
所以这对德普先生来说很糟糕 甚至可能很快变得更糟
so this thing could get real bad, even worse, real fast for Mr. Depp.
我今天站出来 是因为她没有支持者
I thought it was important to come out because she didn't really have any supporters out here,
尤其是今天 只有我站了出来
um, I think especially today. I'm the only one out here.
天啊 我的心在狂跳
Man, my heart is racing.
这真的像…
It is literally like, "Whoo!"
我从来没有因为一个判决如此紧张过
I am... I've never been this nervous for a verdict before.
（经过陪审团三天的审议）
（社交媒体评论员）
（在期待万分地直播每一个时刻）
我们还有五分钟 各位 会是怎样的结果？
So we've got literally five minutes. So guys, which way is it gonna go?
我问过你们了 投票显示
I've asked you, and on the poll,
你们中有高达74%的人 认为约翰尼会赢
it's gone up to 74% of you think that Johnny will win,
排第二的是都不选
with "neither" being the next choice.
所以 你们现在在法庭上了
So, you're in court now.
你生活中无论发生其他任何事情 你都会说：“抱歉 我有…
Whatever else is going on in your life, it's like, "I'm sorry, I have...
法院重新开庭了”
Court has resumed."
哦 老巫婆来了 她来了
Oh, here's the barn witch. Here she is.
该死
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
她看起来很开心
She looks so happy.
我等不及看到这个笑容变成哭脸了
Oh, I can't wait to see that smile turn upside down.
上帝保佑
Fingers crossed, fingers crossed.
只有赫德出庭了 德普现在在英国
Yeah, Amber Heard is the only one in court. Johnny Depp is currently in the UK.
他不在法庭上
He's not at the courtroom.
她去了法庭 赫德
She's gone to the courtroom, Amber Heard,
显然 她的人已经在说
and is apparently...her people are already saying,
“这已经不言自明了吧？”
"Well, doesn't this say it all?"
准备迎接陪审团
Ready for the jury.
“他在那边的摇滚演唱会上寻欢作乐”
"He's gallivanting on a rock concert over there."
他们看起来无动于衷 聊天室的各位怎么看？
They look stoic. What do you guys think in the chat?
不知道陪审团在看谁
I wonder who the jury's looking at.
好了 陪审团主席 这是陪审团的裁决结果吗？
All right, Mr. Foreperson, is this the verdict of the jury?
-是的 -好 全体一致吗？
- Yes, Your Honor. - All right, is it unanimous?
是的
Yes, Your Honor.
好 我们来看看
All right, let's see it.
民事案件CL2019 2911中
In civil case number CL-2019...
德普先生对赫德小姐的指控
...Mr. Depp's claim against Ms. Heard.
来吧
Here we go.
第一 关于出现在网上的评论文章
- One, as to the statement...appearing in the online op-ed entitled,
“安柏・赫德：
"Amber Heard:
我大声疾呼反对性暴力 直面了我们文化的愤怒”
I Spoke Up...statement one, the headline. "...and Faced our Culture's Wrath,"
你们是否认为德普先生 已经证明了诽谤的所有要素？
do you find that Mr. Depp has proven all the elements of defamation?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
-轰！ -哇！
- Boom! - Damn!
德普先生有没有通过更多证据证明
Depp wins count one.
问题 该陈述 是由赫德女士作出或发表的？
...the statement was made or published by Ms. Heard?
回答 是的
- Answer, yes. - Wow!
提出的问题 陈述是关于德普先生？
The stated question, the statement was about Mr. Depp?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
问题 陈述是错误的？
Question, the statement was false?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
问题 该陈述对德普先生
Question, the statement has a defamatory implication
有诽谤暗示？
about Mr. Depp?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
耶！
Yeah!
提出问题 该陈述是关于德普先生的
It's gone Johnny's way.
你们是否认为德普先生 已经证明了诽谤的所有要素？
Do you find that Mr. Depp has proven...all the elements of defamation?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
问题 诽谤性暗示 是由赫德小姐设计和有意为之的？
Question, defamatory implication was designed and intended by Ms. Heard?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
问题 你们是否认为德普先生 已经证明了诽谤的所有要素？
Question, do you find that Mr. Depp has proven all the elements of defamation?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
（摇摆摇摆）
德普先生有没有通过更多证据证明
Has Mr. Depp proven by a greater weight of the evidence,
问题 诽谤性暗示 是由赫德小姐设计和有意为之的？
question, the defamatory implication...was designed and intended by Ms. Heard?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
全都回答都是“是的”
All yesses.
天啊
Holy shit.
哇
Wow.
我们陪审团裁定赔偿损失一千万美元
We the jury award compensatory damages in the amount of ten million dollars.
耶！
Yeah!
一千万美元！
Ten million dollars!
我们陪审团裁定 判处五百万美元的惩罚性赔偿
We the jury award punitive damages in the amount of five million dollars.
太好了！
- Oh! - Yes!
我的天
Oh, my God.
你们是否认为 赫德小姐证明了诽谤的全部要素？
Do you find that Ms. Heard has proven all the elements of defamation?
回答 是的
Answer, yes.
对于约翰C德普二世
As against John C. Depp II,
我们陪审团裁定赔偿损失二百万美元
we the jury award compensatory damages in the amount of two million dollars.
女士们 先生们 你们在本案中的工作到此结束
Ladies and gentlemen, this concludes your service on this case.
我要再次感谢你们 在这次审判中的奉献和辛勤工作
I wanna thank you again for your dedication and your hard work during this trial,
我知道这句话代表了这里的每一个人
and I know I speak for everybody here.
约翰尼！
Johnny! Johnny! Johnny! Johnny! Johnny! Johnny!
约翰尼・德普和安柏・赫德的 诽谤案宣读了判决
Johnny Depp and Amber Heard defamation trial announced its verdict,
判决约翰尼・德普胜诉
ruling in favor of Johnny Depp.
爱你 约翰尼！
Love you, Johnny! We love you, Johnny! We lo...
（英国纽卡斯尔的酒吧 判决当天）
约翰尼 我爱你 兄弟
Oi, John, Johnny, Johnny, Johnny, I love you, bro. I love you, bro.
一场如此残酷的战役 却没有获得太多胜利
A verdict with little victory when the battle has been so brutal.
安柏・赫德不是一个好证人 陪审团对此给出了反馈
Amber Heard was not a good witness, and juries react to that.
我觉得陪审团弄错了
I think the jury got it wrong, Jake.
我对陪审团的判决非常失望
I'm very disappointed in the jury verdict.
我认为这是强权男人的 又一次巨大胜利
I think this is another big win for powerful men,
对女人来说是巨大的失败
and it's a colossal loss for women.
（在判决之后）
（社交媒体上有部分人 为安柏・赫德激情发声）
（但大部分人在庆祝）
这是一种羞辱性的仪式 意在让女人认清自己的位置
This was a humiliation ritual intending to put women in their place.
如果你说出自己遭受虐待
If you speak out about abuse,
将会付出代价
there will be consequences.
这是我们都想要的判决 各位
It was the verdict we all wanted, guys.
约翰尼・德普 德普 德普！
Johnny Depp, Depp, Depp! Johnny Depp, Depp, Depp!
（约翰尼・德普赢了）
（在德普的众多网络支持者 庆祝他的胜利的同时）
（部分新闻媒体开始提出质疑）
我们羞辱赫德时获得的快感
The pleasure with which we're humiliating Amber Heard
跟我们对 约翰尼・德普的美化一样可怕
is... is just as, I... I think, troubling as... as the glamorization of... of... of Johnny Depp in this story.
当那是一个我们认识的人 我们可能很喜欢的人时
When it's somebody that we know, somebody that we maybe like,
他们不愿思考
they don't wanna have to think
这个人真的可能 做出法庭上指控他的那些事
this person is really capable of doing what's alleged in court.
我收到的关于这个话题的邮件 比以往任何话题的都多
I've never had as many emails, uh, as I've received about this very topic.
我听过被虐待过的男性
I've heard from men who have been, uh, abused,
我听过不相信赫德的女性幸存者
I've heard from women who are survivors who don't believe Amber Heard
说她在伤害幸存者 公众有各种各样的情绪
and say she's hurting, uh, survivors. So there's a lot of feelings out there.
（我支持安柏）
我希望这次审判能让大家警觉
But one of the things I hope that this trial raises some awareness of
家庭暴力的复杂性和性别影响
is the complexity of domestic violence and some of the gendered implications of it,
尤其是提到家庭暴力的男性受害者
particularly when we're talking about male victims of domestic violence.
（判决日当天）
（一个家暴幸存者群体）
（写了一封给赫德的公开信）
这封有力的公开信 说明他们并不支持她
This powerful open letter states that they don't stand with her,
他们不接受 她是她自己所声称的那个人
they don't accept that she is who she claimed to be.
“我们不会支持你”
"We will not stand with you."
“没有任何家庭暴力受害者 会有你那样的表现”
“我们支持过你 为你哭泣过
"We supported you, we wept for you,
我们为你宣传
we rallied behind you,
而你背叛了我们所有人
and you betrayed us all."
听到你说的话 让我们中的很多人
感到巨大痛苦 引发不好的回忆 甚至无法忍受”
你的行为影响了未来 报告遭受家庭暴力的女性们
你提醒了很多幸存者 虐待不分性别
一个说出自己遭受虐待的男人 也必须被听到
你把我们的运动 作为武器来对付你的受害者
这一切是为了什么？
你说“是你逼我这么做的”的时候
我们就知道你真正的身份了 虐待者 你的受害者是约翰尼
他是幸存者
我觉得非常受刺激 再次体验了创伤
I'm feeling incredibly triggered and re-traumatized
我也是曾经经历过亲密关系暴力的人
as someone who's experienced relationship abuse in the past,
但我不是代替约翰尼・德普受刺激
but I'm not feeling triggered on behalf of Johnny Depp.
我们所看到的现状
What we're seeing happen, stereotypes that are coming out, right,
刻板印象出现了 说安柏・赫德是骗子
uh, that were calling A-Amber Heard a liar,
将约翰尼・德普 美化成一个了不起的男人
who... glorifying, uh, Johnny Depp as-as-as-as this amazing man, right,
这就是“我也是运动”开始的原因
um, is the reason why Me Too started.
这就是为什么 活动家们想为这一刻而战
It's the... It's... It's...it's why activists really wanted to fight for this movement
以及这为何如此重要 因为女人没有感觉到
and why it's so important, because women didn't feel,
以及所有性别的幸存者
and... and, you know, survivors of all genders,
不觉得他们可以举报 不觉得这个举动是合理的
didn't feel like they could report, didn't feel like it was gonna be welcome.
这是什么意思？ “我也是运动”到头了？
What does it mean for that? Are we at the end of Me Too?
这是逆转吗？我们现在是什么情况？
Is this a reversal? Wh... Where are we?
这是对“我也是运动”的反弹
I mean, it's a backlash to Me Too,
我们看到互联网展示出的现状
and what we're seeing unfold on the Internet
我们在证明他们是正确的
is that we're proving them right.
我们在说：“是的 你会被噤声 你会被羞辱”
We're... We're... We're saying that, "Yes, you will be silenced, you will be humiliated."
我不会站边
I'm not taking any sides.
听起来赫德的确在他们交往期间
It sounds like Heard did allegedly do some malicious shit
做过据说很糟糕的事情
during the course of their relationship.
但赫德每天都在 全球范围内被疯狂攻击
But I am feeling some kind of way about the way that Heard is being inhumanely attacked
也让我很不是滋味
every day on a global scale.
这就是暴力受害者的处境
And here's what this means for victims of abuse,
挺身而出的人会越来越少
fewer victims will come forward,
尤其是如果他们 在那段关系中也不完美的话
especially if they haven't been perfect during the course of their relationship with the abuser.
如果你因为做错了某件事 不是完美的受害者
So if you're not the perfect victim because you did something wrong,
你反抗了 你就是不完美的人
you fought back, you're an imperfect person,
全世界都会对你进行极致的羞辱
then the world will lob every available insult at you
让你闭嘴
to get you to shut up.
（判决后第二天 安柏赫德的律师）
（伊莱恩・布雷德霍夫特 接受了NBC的采访）
首先 安柏状态如何？
First question, how is Amber doing?
她最开始说的话就是
One of the first things she said is,
“我对所有 有相似经历的女人感到抱歉”
"I am so sorry to all those women out there."
这对法庭内外的女人来说都是打击
This is a setback for all women in and outside the courtroom.
我想问问社交媒体的事
Let me ask you about social media.
那上面的声音完全是一边倒 而且对安柏赫德的攻击非常尖锐
It was incredibly lopsided and vitriolic against Amber Heard.
你觉得那对案件结果有影响吗？
Do you think that had an effect on the case?
-当然 -你觉得陪审团知道吗？
- Absolutely. - You think jurors were aware?
怎么会不知道？他们每天晚上都回家
How can you not? They went home every night.
他们有家人 家人会上社交媒体
They have families, the families are on social media.
（一周后 约翰尼・德普的律师们 接受了NBC的采访）
你们觉得陪审员们看到了那些 有被网上的声音影响吗？
Do you believe the jurors saw any of that, were swayed by any of that?
不 我不认为有任何理由相信 陪审员们违背了他们的誓言
No. I don't think there's any reason to believe that the jurors violated their oath.
他们在中间有十天的休息时间 因为有一个司法会议
...had a ten-day break in the middle because of the judicial conference.
那些信息不可能对他们毫无影响 而且它们非常可怕
There's no way they couldn't have been influenced by it, and it was horrible.
无处不在 但与此同时 他们每晚都在被告诫
It is everywhere, but at the same time, they were admonished every single night,
他们非常尊重法庭和程序
and, uh, they had an... tremendous amount of respect, I think, for the court and the process,
而且他们都尽力了
and they were doing the best that they could.
我反对在法庭里架摄像机
I... I was against cameras in the courtroom.
我公开反对过这种做法 因为这起案件的性质敏感
And I went on record with that, and... and had argued against it because of the sensitive nature of this.
法庭变成了动物园
But it made it a zoo.
允许摄像机进入庭审 就是对抖音玩梗敞开了大门
By allowing cameras into the trial, you opened up the space for TikTok memes.
（阿雅罗曼诺 文化记者 说出三首歌播客音频）
的确有针锋相对的社交媒体话题
I mean, you did have, obviously, like, competing social media hashtags, right...
支持其中一方或者另一方
...in support for one or the other.
但很多研究表明 约翰尼・德普的话题
But there was a lot of research showing that the hashtags for Johnny Depp
在全网大规模地被创造出来 并且被大肆传播
had been essentially created and proliferated and manipulated
以及被操控
far and wide across the Internet.
（迈克尔・霍布斯 记者 爸爸取消我播客嘉宾）
有人说是机器人
People say it's bots.
这场审判的错误信息 规模之大是史无前例的
The scale of, like, the misinformation about this trial is truly unprecedented.
我在看赫德的律师接受采访
Okay, I'm watching this interview with Amber Heard's lawyer.
她很会表达
She's very articulate, by the way,
这和她在社交媒体上 被刻画出来的形象截然不同
which is completely in contrast to the way that she was portrayed on social media.
所以我看了一下评论 里面充斥着诋毁之词
And so, naturally, go to check out the comments, they're all very disparaging.
它们还获得了很多点赞 1.6万 2.5万 3.3万
They're racking up tons of likes, 16,000, 25,000, 33,000,
但你点进他们的资料 都是假的
but when you actually go to click into these profiles, they're all fake.
这些都不是真人
Like, none of these people are real.
毫无内容
Zero content.
然后你开始意识到 这些可能是机器人
And then you start to realize, like, these are probably bots.
当你点进视频发布者的资料
And when you actually click on the profile of the person who posted this video,
那是一个约翰尼・德普超级粉丝 的账户 估计也是机器人
it's a super pro-Johnny Depp fan account, which is probably a bot too.
我们受到了机器人之间互动的影响
We're being influenced by bots interacting with bots interacting with bots.
你们知道那场网络营销的事情吗？
Do you know anything about an online campaign,
作为德普的代理律师
uh, on behalf of Johnny Depp?
那完全是荒谬且毫无事实根据的
That was absolutely absurd and baseless.
你们确切地知道他和他的经纪公司
And... And you know for a fact that neither he nor his agents nor anyone
都没有付费进行 任何的社交媒体营销吗？
tried to, in some way, pay for or otherwise encourage this kind of social media...
-绝对没有 -绝对
- Categorically false. Categorically false. - Categorically?
我的天！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
太好了！
Yes!
他看了我们 还指了我们！
Johnny just looked at us and pointed at us!
我得谢谢你
- Thank you. - Than... Well, I gotta thank you.
我经历过类似的事 我为你感到骄傲
- No, man. - I... I've been through a similar thing. And I'm just so proud of you. I'm so proud of you.
你没有放弃 你确保人们听到了真相
You... You didn't give up. It helped make sure people heard the truth.
各位 我见到了约翰尼・德普
Guys, I met Johnny Depp.
我说的见到 不只是跟他握手
I'm not just saying I shook his hand,
我和约翰尼・德普共度了美好时光
I spent time, quality time, with Johnny Depp.
你们是勇士
You... You... You... You guys were the warriors. I mean...
我太惊讶了
It... It... It... It stunned me.
我非常震惊 你们所有人
It... It stunned me that... that all of you could...
聚在一起 让我从那场恐怖节目中
that all of you got together and... and...
能够脱身而出
lifted me above the... the, um...the horror show.
是的
Yeah.
你知道吗？
You know?
对了 我从你们身上学到了好多
By the way, I learned so much from you guys.
我看着你们就学到了好多
I learned so much from watching you guys.
这起案子虽然取得了判决
This is the case that, though there is a verdict,
但它不会结束的 为什么？
just will not end. Why?
因为赫德没有停止讲这件事
Because Amber Heard has not stopped talking about this case.
她接受了萨凡纳・古瑟瑞的独家访谈
She sat down for an exclusive interview with Savannah Guthrie.
你会想听听的
You guys are gonna wanna hear this one.
就算你觉得我在撒谎
Even if you think that I'm lying,
你还是不能看着我的眼睛 告诉我你认为社交媒体上
you still couldn't look me in the eye and tell me that you think, on social media,
我和他得到了公平的代表
there's been a fair representation.
是的 因为你撒谎了 公众不会再轻信你的鬼话了
Yeah, because you lied! And the public didn't buy...isn't falling for your nonsense anymore.
-陪审团不会对此免疫 -你觉得陪审团看到了？
- The jury's not immune to that. - You think the jury saw it?
他们怎么可能没看到？
How could they not?
就算是最善意的陪审员 也不可能完全避免接触到
I think even the most well-intentioned juror, it would have been impossible to avoid this.
嗨 安迪的爆米花星球的观众
Hi, everybody there on, um, Andy's, um, Popcorned Planet.
我只能说谢谢你们
I've... I can only say thank you
这是我内心深处的感激
from... from the... from the very recesses of, uh...
谢谢你们做的一切 对我的关心
of my being, um, for all...for everything, for being f... around for me,
谢谢你们的支持 谢谢你们
for your support, and, uh...thank you.
谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
很多幸存者都想感谢你 谢谢你做的一切 难以置信
A lot of survivors wanna thank you. Thank you for everything, man. Incredible.
（社交媒体评论员）
（迅速对赫德的新访谈进行了分析）
（数周后 她仍然是网上被攻击的靶子）
有很多人也认同 觉得你在撒谎
There's an abundance of people who also agree and think that you're lying,
我们都在生你的气
that we all are angry at you.
德普团队声称你才是施暴者
The Depp team argued that you were the abuser.
我从未主动挑事 我都是做出反应 当你在…
I never had to instigate it, I responded to it. When you're liv...
“我从未主动挑事”
"I never had to instigate it."
她相信自己说的每一个词
She believes every word she's saying.
很妙的反转
Nice spin there.
还有一些时刻 有一个录音里 你在嘲讽他
Then there are other times, there's another tape, where you're taunting him,
“告诉全世界 约翰尼・德普
and saying, "Oh..."
我 一个男人 也是家庭暴力的受害者”
"...I, a man, am a victim of domestic violence."
-我也是家庭暴力的受害者 -是的
20秒的片段
Twenty-second clips.
所以这一段话并不能代表
So the transcripts of them...are not representative
提取出那段话的两三个小时的对话
of two hours, or the three hours those clips are excerpt from.
不能代表是什么意思？ 当然能代表 都录音录下来了
What? What do you mean, it doesn't represent it? What... What do you mean by that? Yeah, it does! 'Cause... 'Cause it's in... It's in the recording!
你不能坐在那里张嘴就来 “那不能代表…” 就是能代表
You can't sit there and say, "Well, it doesn't represent the whole..." It does.
安柏・赫德想让 约翰尼・德普成为一个角色
Amber Heard wanted to characterize Johnny Depp as a character.
审判产生了很多梗 现在那场访谈又有了一些梗
There were many memes from the trial, but now memes from the... Now memes from the interview.
德普的律师称你的证词
The Depp lawyer said... called your testimony,
“人生中最棒的表演” 说你是在演戏
"The performance of a lifetime," and said you were acting.
你有什么看法？
What do you say to that?
明明那个律师的当事人
Says the lawyer
让全世界都相信他有剪刀手
for the man who convinced the world he had scissors for fingers?
（还有没有人看过这部纪录片）
（这个人的手指都是剪刀！）
你是想告诉我 那个傻瓜一直在骗我们吗？
You mean to tell me that that fool was lying to us the whole time?
他的手不是真的用剪刀做的吗？
His hands were not really made of scissors?
（2022年8月 弗吉尼亚）
（判决后两个月）
我们想细说的是陪审团没看到的东西
What we really wanna get into right now is what the jury didn't see,
这场审判的过程中不被允许看的东西
what wasn't allowed during the course of this trial.
这起案子解封了超过6000份文件
Over 6,000 documents have been unsealed in this case.
（此事应予解封）
这本会对陪审团的决定造成影响的
This would have been very relevant for the jury to hear.
如果你想要那些文件
If you wanted to get hold of those documents,
你必须去弗吉尼亚法院提出请求
you had to go to the Virginia courthouse and make a request,
德普的粉丝众筹了一笔钱 买到了解封的文件
so JD fans crowdfunded getting hold of the unsealed documents.
（只用超过3300美元 就能解封超过6600页的文件）
（欢迎捐款）
安卓雅・伯克哈特
Andrea Burkhart,
YouTube评论员和刑事辩护律师
who is a YouTube commentator and is a criminal defense attorney,
众筹资金购买
she crowdsourced the funds in order to buy these documents.
如果你一直在关注这起案子
If you've been watching this case for a while,
你就会知道安柏・赫德有个习惯
you know that Amber Heard has a habit
她会隐瞒无法被证实的信息
of hiding behind information that can't be verified.
但这看起来可能不是这样
But it looks like that might not be the case.
造成这一局面的是
What spurred this
是他们在法庭上签署判决书和赔偿时
was when they were in court to sign the judgment and sentence,
阿兹卡瑞特法官表明
Judge Azcarate voiced her intention
她打算解封曾被封存的材料
to unseal materials that had previously been sealed,
她说有很多东西被封存了
and she said that many of the things were sealed
因为我们不想让陪审团受到负面影响
because we didn't want to have any taint to the jury.
所以如果安柏・赫德 希望让这些东西保密
So if Amber Heard was hoping to keep all of this stuff secret,
我认为她会发现自己很不走运
I think she's gonna find herself out of luck.
我们回到飞机事件上
Let's go back to the... there was a plane incident
德普据称 在一架飞机上踢了安柏・赫德
where Depp allegedly kicked Amber Heard on a plane.
我相信是在2014年
I believe it was in 2014.
你有没有看到德普先生 在飞机上脚踢或者互扔东西？
Did you observe Mr. Depp kick or throw anything at each other on the plane?
不 我完全没有这个印象
No, I don't recall that at all.
约翰尼・德普的助理史蒂芬杜特斯
There were texts from Johnny Depp's assistant,
给安柏・赫德发了短信
Stephen Deuters, to Amber Heard, quote...
“如果有人对他说实话 告诉他那件事有多糟糕…
（解封文件 美国审判 2022年）
…他会感到震惊的
我很难过他没有更好的途径
知道他昨天的行为有多严重
我的不幸在于
我完整地记得那件事 所有细节 发生过的一切”
“他非常震惊
当我跟他说他踢了你 他哭了”
为什么没有公布这些短信？
Why was these text messages not introduced?
这对于安柏・赫德的自证非常关键
I mean, this felt very pivotal for Amber Heard's case.
法庭裁定这些证据
The court ruled on those that they're irrelevant
与当下的诽谤案无关
to the... the case at hand of defamation.
这起案子有太多的证据 现在我们看到了更多
You know, there was so much evidence in this case, and now we're seeing even more of the evidence,
在预审听证会上
and... and in the pre-trial hearings,
他们必须决定 哪些证据可以采纳 哪些不能
they have to, you know, rule what is admissible, what isn't.
其中一些真的很难界定
And, yeah, there's some of these things that are really on the line
到底应不应该被采纳
of whether they should or shouldn... shouldn't have been admissible.
德普的支持者 很不喜欢德普在周末发布的
Depp supporters have been unliking Depp's victory post
宣告胜利的帖文
over the weekend.
（最好的还在后面 一个新的篇章已经开始）
在法官裁定 与本案无关的审前文件被公开后
The discovery of the unlikes has come after the unsealing
人们开始不喜欢德普
of pretrial documents that the judge ruled not relevant to the case.
我们今天要深入了解这些事 这样你们可以自己判定
We're gonna dive into all of these things today so you can decide for yourself.
之前被封存的法庭文件 显示德普和他助理往来的短信
"Previously sealed court documents, they revealed texts from Depp and his assistant
全部都在证实赫德的指控
all but confirming Heard's allegation
指控称他曾在一家私人飞机上 当着员工的面 脚踢和殴打赫德
he'd kicked and beat her in front of his staff on a private plane."
（德普粉丝付费三千美元 解封法庭文件 以寻找安柏黑料）
（结果找到约翰尼的黑料）
赫德和史蒂芬杜特斯
在2014年5月24日和25日 之间的任何短信往来
虽然此前拷贝过杜特斯先生的手机
德普先生还是无法定位
在赫德小姐制造出 “波士顿飞机事件”之后
赫德和杜特斯之间的一系列短信往来
（史蒂芬・杜特斯声称 那些短信被“严重篡改”）
（他说自己从未见过 约翰尼对安柏有过肢体暴力）
（德普作证称自己 “这辈子”都没有打过女人）
奇怪的是 赫德小姐 拿出的短信的格式
跟她的其他短信格式都不一样
这些文本的真实性至关重要 然而受到了严重质疑
"The veracity of these text messages is critical and subject to serious question."
所以真相是什么？
So what is the truth?
（妮可拉宾 金钱戒疗中心播客音频）
我无法回答关于这件事真相的问题
This question of the truth of the matter I can't answer.
事实上 没人能回答
In fact, no one can.
没人知道这两个人之间发生了什么
No one knows what happened between these two people.
听上去有证据证明 他们相互都有过暴力行为
Sounds like there is evidence that they were both abusive toward each other,
但很多都是各执一词
but it's a lot of "he said, she said,"
而且几乎不可能找到解决办法和真相
and it's nearly impossible to find resolution and truth.
公众是第二个陪审团
The public is a... a second jury.
我们自己做的决定动摇了舆论
Us making up our own decisions and... really swayed on people's public opinion,
包括陪审团对他们两个人的看法
including the jurors', of these two characters.
被指控做错事的人…
People who've been accused of wrongdoing,
（茱莉亚・雅各布斯 《纽约时报》播客音频）
…目标是获得某种正义 他们在寻求自己的救赎
the goal is to get a form of justice, a sense of redemption for themselves.
重点在于洗清自己的名声 并试图在舆论法庭上
It's about clearing their name and trying to establish
确立这段关系或事件的真相
what the truth was of this relationship or this incident in a public court of law.
他已经在舆论法庭上获胜了
He's won already in the court of opinion,
而他还需要通过司法程序 洗清自己的名声
and he needed the court process to clear his name.
正义的重点其实不是真相
The thing is about justice is that it's not about the truth,
无关对错
it's not about right or wrong,
而是法官或陪审员相信什么
it's about what the judge or jury believes.
（尼克・维尔 电视嘉宾 维尔档案播客主播）
我们生活在这样的时代
We now live in a time
我们不一定相信正义的人
where we don't necessarily believe who's right...
我们相信自己最喜欢的人 因为他们的身份
...we believe who we like the most because of who they are.
这场审判的结果将产生影响
The outcome of this trial will have ramification,
至少会改变 人们如何相信其他人的故事
if nothing else, how people believe people and their stories.
（德普 vs 赫德： 好莱坞夫妻诽谤案）
（我们应该信任谁）
（2022年12月 双方同意和解）
（安柏・赫德同意 向约翰尼・德普支付100万美元）
（她声称网络暴力 是她作出这个决定的原因之一）
（社交媒体上的辩论仍然激烈）
字幕翻译：Zeo Niu